Guide to the Albert Leroy Andrews correspondence, 1899-1964.
Andrews, Albert Leroy correspondence, 1899-1964.
- Series I. Correspondence on Bryology
  - Robinson, B.L., 1899-1904 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Rogers, Donald P., 1946-1953 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Rogerson, Clark T., Jan. 9, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Roine, G., Feb. 26, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Rol, R. (see also: Jovet-Ast, S.), June 18, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Rollins, Reed C., June 16, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Ropes, Marian E., June 9, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Roth, Dr. Gg., 1906-1914 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Rousseau, Jacques, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Rugg, Harold G., 1942 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Russell, W.S.C., Mar. 24, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Sainsbury, George O.K., 1937-1956 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Sargent, C.S., Feb. 12, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Sasaoka, H., 1920-1921 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Sayre, Geneva, Oct. 21, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Sbarbaro, Camillo, Aug. 13, (?) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Schallert, Paul O., 1922-1955 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Scheepers, John T., Sept. 28, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Schnooberger, Irma, 1940-1957 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Schofield, Wilfred B., 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Schornherst, Ruth, 1938-1946 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Schramm, J.R., Aug. 29, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Schumacher, Alb., 1934-1937 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Schuster, Olga M. (see also: Schuster, R.M.), 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Schuster, Rudolf M. (see also: Schuster, O.M.), 1947-1961 (Box 7, Folder 14-15)
  - Seaver, Fred J., 1944-1946 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Sharp, Aaron Jack, 1930-1961 (Box 7, Folder 17-20)
  - Shelar, Keller, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Sheldon, John L., 1909; 1932 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Sherrard, Elizabeth M., 1953-1957 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Shields, A. Randolph, Mar. 28, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Showalter, A.M., 1929 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Sutch, Alexander F., 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Small, John K., July 22, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Smith, Annie Merrill, 1908-1913 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Smith, Lucy Cranwell, 1945-1955 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Smith, Rowland F., Apr. 16, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Smith, Stanley Jay, 1955-1961 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Soderberg, Ivar, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Sperling, Jon A., Apr. 16, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Stauffer, R. Eliot, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Steere, William Campbell, 1933-1958 (Box 7, Folder 35-38)
  - Stegermark, Julian A., Feb. 28, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Stifler, Cloyd Burnley, Sept. 13, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Stone, Witmer, July 11, 1921 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Stormer, Per, May 28, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Stoutmeyer, V.T., 1943 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Suzuki, Hyoji (Mr.), 1952-1955 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Svihla, Ruth Dowell, Feb. 26, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Tavares, Isabelle, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Taylor, Charles A., Jr., May 6, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Taylor, Edward C., 1957 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Taylor, Jane, 1952-1954 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Taylor, Wm. Randolph, 1922; 1958 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Thaxter, Roland, 1921-1922 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Theriot, M. Irene, 1912; 1930 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Thomson, R.B., 1918 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Thorpe, Frances J., Jan. 16, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Tremper, John S., 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - True, Rodney H., Oct. 19, 1903 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Urban, I., May 7, 1910 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Van Schaak, George B., 1947 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Vanderspek, John W., Oct. 12, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Verdoorn, Frans, 1931-1941 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Voth, Paul D., 1939 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Wad, A., Aug. 2, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Wagenknecht, Austin C., Sept. 26, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Wagner, Kenneth A., 1949; 1957 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Wallace, E.C., Aug. 20, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Wareham, Richard T., 1936-1946 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Warnsdorf, C., 1904-1913 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Watson, E.V., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Weber, Willaim A., 1949; 1960 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Welch, Winona H., 1934-1961 (Box 8, Folder 25-26)
  - Whitaker, Ellis H., Aug. 12, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - White, Marcus W., 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - White, Margaret, 1960-9161 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Whitehouse, Eula, 1950-1954 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Whitney, Elsie Gibson, Sept. 10, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Wickes, Mildred L., 1936-1942 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Wiegand, K.M., 1917-1931 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Wilkes, James C., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Williams, Emile F., 1903-1904 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Williams, Henry, Apr. 7, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Williams, R.S., 1914-1922; 1929-1940 (Box 8, Folder 37-38)
  - Willis, J.H., 1951-1953 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Wislon, Lilias Gordon, Aug. 7, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Winne, William T., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Winter, D., Nov. 13, 1906 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Wolfe, John N., May 3, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Wolfe, Katherine A., 1930 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Worthley, Elmer G., 1956-1959 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Wright, Forrest B., May 9, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Illegible Correspondence, July 14, 1901; Feb. 15, 1910;; Dec. 13, 1911; (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Illegible Correspondence, June 23, 1916; June 25, 1918;; Apr. 18, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Misc. photos of A.L. Andrews (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Alphabetical listing of correspondents and others which includes notes and questions concerning the determinations of bryological specimens (pages photocopied from original slip lists), 1909-1961 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Series II. Family Correspondence
  - 1905 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Jan. 1906-Mar. 1906 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Apr. 1906-June 1906 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - July 1906-Oct. 1906 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Nov. 1906-Dec. 1906, Sept. 1907-Oct. 1907 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 1948, 1956, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 6)